

# **NGUYEN VAN A**

### **MARKETING MANAGER**

Male

**May 19, 1992** 

Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and idatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

### **EDUCATION**



### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. ill, which is the same as saying through sh administration

m Sep 2007 - Present

#### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. corporate administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

### **EXPERIENCE**



Sep 2007 - Present

#### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

#### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult with a man who chooses to enjoy a pleasure that has no annoying consequences, or one who av and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

#### **Recognition and Gains:**

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

#### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to nally circumstances occur in wh goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working





Sep 2003 - 2007

### **CVPRO JSC**

### Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer ham reads: "Nor is there anyone who lo' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

## **CERTIFICATIONS**



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2004

# HONORS & AWARDS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2013 - 2014

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US e 1914 translati

#### **REFERENCES**



### **NGUYEN VAN BINH**

director of cvpro jsc

### **SKILLS**



Words Photoshop

Excel English

Power Point Japanese

### **INTERESTS**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt ite wi and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities